(Howard(voice):)Let me know. It's Howard.
[CLICKS]
- I've had her brisket. Melts in your mouth.
- Mm-hm.
(Steph:)Maybe we should think about
going to the bedroom.
That's a good idea, because there's a bed
there, and I'm very, very, very pro-bed.
[PHONE RINGS]
STEPHANIE: You've reached
Dr. Stephanie Barnett. Leave a message.
[PHONE BEEPS]
HOWARD:
Hey, it's me again.
Just wanna let you know the head count
for dinner Friday has gone up.
(Howard(voice):)My Aunt Betty and Uncle Elliot are coming
in from Palm Springs.
(Howard(voice):)Oh, and if anybody should ask,
you're half Jewish on your mother's side.
(Howard(voice):)Okay, call me. It's Howard.
[CLICKS]
Don't you think you should tell him
you're not interested?
(Steph:)You want me to stop
and call him back right now?
(Leonard:)Dear God, no.